[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "... and most of his party think he's crackers (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["...", "and", "most", "of", "his", "party", "think", "he", "'s", "crackers", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "For once in a while I'm extremely grateful for your British roots.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "once", "in", "a", "while", "I", "'m", "extremely", "grateful", "for", "your", "British", "roots", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "What he really thinks of Vladimir Putin?", "question_tokens": ["What", "he", "really", "thinks", "of", "Vladimir", "Putin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Smart and remarkably -- we had a really good blunt relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["Smart", "and", "remarkably", "--", "we", "had", "a", "really", "good", "blunt", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vladimir Putin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "How blunt?", "question_tokens": ["How", "blunt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "Brutally blunt.", "answer_tokens": ["Brutally", "blunt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "What is your take on on where we are?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "on", "where", "we", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Well, first, all the problems are probably being intensified by the economic challenges we face.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "all", "the", "problems", "are", "probably", "being", "intensified", "by", "the", "economic", "challenges", "we", "face", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBN", "-NONE-", "NN", ":", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "How much do you trust him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "do", "you", "trust", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "LINTON: Well, first of all, I think it's an interesting commentary on the world in which we're living that admitting that the holocaust occurred, qualified (ph) as being a moderate.", "answer_tokens": ["LINTON", ":", "Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "an", "interesting", "commentary", "on", "the", "world", "in", "which", "we", "'re", "living", "that", "admitting", "that", "the", "holocaust", "occurred", ",", "qualified", "(", "ph", ")", "as", "being", "a", "moderate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "And it's just going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "'s", "just", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "No, we don't have to believe it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "believe", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What was he like behind closed doors away from, you know, the public utterances?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "behind", "closed", "doors", "away", "from", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "public", "utterances", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Smart and remarkably -- we had a really good blunt relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["Smart", "and", "remarkably", "--", "we", "had", "a", "really", "good", "blunt", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "How blunt?", "question_tokens": ["How", "blunt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Brutally blunt.", "answer_tokens": ["Brutally", "blunt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Did you talked to him on the phone?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "talked", "to", "him", "on", "the", "phone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Can you just share with us a little bit about why you think that's so important?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "just", "share", "with", "us", "a", "little", "bit", "about", "why", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "so", "important", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Well, coming to your family as you're talking women in the workforce, who do you think might make the better president, your wife or your daughter?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "coming", "to", "your", "family", "as", "you", "'re", "talking", "women", "in", "the", "workforce", ",", "who", "do", "you", "think", "might", "make", "the", "better", "president", ",", "your", "wife", "or", "your", "daughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "The day after tomorrow, my wife because she's had more experience.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "day", "after", "tomorrow", ",", "my", "wife", "because", "she", "'s", "had", "more", "experience", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Can you put as all out of our misery?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "put", "as", "all", "out", "of", "our", "misery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "What is the ways first, you and Newt Gingrich eventually worked it up between you -- how do you get stuff done in this dysfunctional Washington?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "ways", "first", ",", "you", "and", "Newt", "Gingrich", "eventually", "worked", "it", "up", "between", "you", "--", "how", "do", "you", "get", "stuff", "done", "in", "this", "dysfunctional", "Washington", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "We worked it out when he was trying to run me out of town.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "worked", "it", "out", "when", "he", "was", "trying", "to", "run", "me", "out", "of", "town", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1996"]}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Why did they do that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "they", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Because consistently, with the single exception of my getting reelected in 1996, the people who agree with us on the gun issue have not been able to protect the people they elect.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "consistently", ",", "with", "the", "single", "exception", "of", "my", "getting", "reelected", "in", "1996", ",", "the", "people", "who", "agree", "with", "us", "on", "the", "gun", "issue", "have", "not", "been", "able", "to", "protect", "the", "people", "they", "elect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Isn't it about political (ph) courage?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "about", "political", "(", "ph", ")", "courage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "No, it is not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "is", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Does he do a good Bono impression?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "do", "a", "good", "Bono", "impression", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "He does.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "He does?", "question_tokens": ["He", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "He does.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Now, first of all, what was your reaction when you heard Bono pretending to be you?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "heard", "Bono", "pretending", "to", "be", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "It was pretty good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "pretty", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "And most certainly got run to America, second thoughts?", "question_tokens": ["And", "most", "certainly", "got", "run", "to", "America", ",", "second", "thoughts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJS", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I'm grateful that I have a proud father.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "grateful", "that", "I", "have", "a", "proud", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Have you ever thought of, you know, running for high office?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "thought", "of", ",", "you", "know", ",", "running", "for", "high", "office", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Well, there's people that's been asking me that question for as long as I can remember, literally.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "people", "that", "'s", "been", "asking", "me", "that", "question", "for", "as", "long", "as", "I", "can", "remember", ",", "literally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "It's true, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "true", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "... this is what I mean.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "this", "is", "what", "I", "mean", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "And if so, who wins?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "so", ",", "who", "wins", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "So, we generally are a card playing family.", "answer_tokens": ["So", ",", "we", "generally", "are", "a", "card", "playing", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Which card games?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "card", "games", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Oh, we play pinochle, spades, hearts, all variant ...", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "we", "play", "pinochle", ",", "spades", ",", "hearts", ",", "all", "variant", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Who wins?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "wins", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Thankfully, it's a pretty equal distribution.", "answer_tokens": ["Thankfully", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "pretty", "equal", "distribution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "You tell me, you all win 33 percent of the time, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "tell", "me", ",", "you", "all", "win", "33", "percent", "of", "the", "time", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "So -- in cards probably.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "--", "in", "cards", "probably", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["33 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130925pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "What are you best at?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "best", "at", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "I do really want a traditional board games, backgammon, checkers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "really", "want", "a", "traditional", "board", "games", ",", "backgammon", ",", "checkers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]